{"sid": "M09FTDZN2H3L_main", "calc_equals_delay": 5, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 331727, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 331728, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["calc_6", 333604], ["calc_+", 334071], ["calc_7", 334722], ["calc_+", 335290], ["calc_7", 335841], ["calc_+", 336356], ["calc_4", 336909], ["calc_3", 337325], ["calc_=", 337757], ["submit", 343554]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "289", "answered_time": 343554, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "289", "question_time_start": 343555, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 347380]], "time_left_end": "285", "answered_time": 347380, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "285", "question_time_start": 347380, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["calc_9", 349849], ["calc_8", 350147], ["calc_+", 350797], ["calc_7", 351413], ["calc_7", 351559], ["calc_=", 352173], ["submit", 364920]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "267", "answered_time": 364920, "user_answer": "183", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "267", "question_time_start": 364920, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 384596]], "time_left_end": "248", "answered_time": 384596, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "248", "question_time_start": 384596, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 389814]], "time_left_end": "242", "answered_time": 389814, "user_answer": "540", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "242", "question_time_start": 389814, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["calc_7", 392749], ["calc_8", 393183], ["calc_+", 393704], ["calc_3", 394417], ["calc_7", 395035], ["calc_+", 395618], ["calc_2", 396352], ["calc_3", 396719], ["calc_+", 397338], ["calc_4", 397887], ["calc_7", 398202], ["calc_=", 398734], ["submit", 405252]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "227", "answered_time": 405252, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "227", "question_time_start": 405252, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 409456]], "time_left_end": "223", "answered_time": 409456, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "223", "question_time_start": 409456, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["submit", 415463]], "time_left_end": "217", "answered_time": 415463, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "217", "question_time_start": 415463, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 419663]], "time_left_end": "213", "answered_time": 419663, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "213", "question_time_start": 419663, "question": "97+56", "correct_answer": 153, "events": [["submit", 423630]], "time_left_end": "209", "answered_time": 423630, "user_answer": "153", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 423630, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "209", "question_time_start": 423630, "question": "4+3+8+64", "correct_answer": 79, "events": [["submit", 433784]], "time_left_end": "198", "answered_time": 433784, "user_answer": "79", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "198", "question_time_start": 433784, "question": "9+83+89", "correct_answer": 181, "events": [["submit", 439122]], "time_left_end": "193", "answered_time": 439122, "user_answer": "181", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "193", "question_time_start": 439122, "question": "83+939", "correct_answer": 1022, "events": [["submit", 456297]], "time_left_end": "176", "answered_time": 456297, "user_answer": "1112", "user_correct": "False", "score": "11"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "176", "question_time_start": 456297, "question": "9+49+83", "correct_answer": 141, "events": [["submit", 470069]], "time_left_end": "162", "answered_time": 470069, "user_answer": "121", "user_correct": "False", "score": "10"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "162", "question_time_start": 470069, "question": "49+78", "correct_answer": 127, "events": [["submit", 473037]], "time_left_end": "159", "answered_time": 473037, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "9"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "159", "question_time_start": 473037, "question": "63+24+74+93", "correct_answer": 254, "events": [["submit", 474108]], "time_left_end": "158", "answered_time": 474108, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "8"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "158", "question_time_start": 474109, "question": "63+848", "correct_answer": 911, "events": [["submit", 474270]], "time_left_end": "158", "answered_time": 474270, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "158", "question_time_start": 474271, "question": "4+76+33", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["submit", 474422]], "time_left_end": "158", "answered_time": 474422, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "6"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "158", "question_time_start": 474422, "question": "6+7+4+33", "correct_answer": 50, "events": [["submit", 474571]], "time_left_end": "158", "answered_time": 474571, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "5"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "158", "question_time_start": 474571, "question": "28+64", "correct_answer": 92, "events": [["submit", 474724]], "time_left_end": "158", "answered_time": 474724, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "4"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 474725, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "158", "question_time_start": 474725, "question": "3+7+3+96", "correct_answer": 109, "events": [["submit", 474873]], "time_left_end": "157", "answered_time": 474873, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "3"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "157", "question_time_start": 474873, "question": "78+56", "correct_answer": 134, "events": [["submit", 475039]], "time_left_end": "157", "answered_time": 475039, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "157", "question_time_start": 475039, "question": "8+97+19", "correct_answer": 124, "events": [["submit", 475190]], "time_left_end": "157", "answered_time": 475190, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "1"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "157", "question_time_start": 475190, "question": "3+4+4+63", "correct_answer": 74, "events": [["submit", 475373]], "time_left_end": "157", "answered_time": 475373, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "0"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "157", "question_time_start": 475373, "question": "23+783", "correct_answer": 806, "events": [["submit", 475540]], "time_left_end": "157", "answered_time": 475540, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-1"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "157", "question_time_start": 475540, "question": "8+84+93", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["submit", 475721]], "time_left_end": "157", "answered_time": 475721, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-2"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "157", "question_time_start": 475722, "question": "4+96+74", "correct_answer": 174, "events": [["submit", 476189]], "time_left_end": "156", "answered_time": 476189, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-3"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "156", "question_time_start": 476189, "question": "38+57+76+29", "correct_answer": 200, "events": [["submit", 476375]], "time_left_end": "156", "answered_time": 476375, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-4"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "156", "question_time_start": 476375, "question": "24+778", "correct_answer": 802, "events": [["submit", 476491]], "time_left_end": "156", "answered_time": 476491, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-5"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "156", "question_time_start": 476492, "question": "87+29", "correct_answer": 116, "events": [["submit", 476620]], "time_left_end": "156", "answered_time": 476620, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-6"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 476620, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "156", "question_time_start": 476620, "question": "76+94+36+16", "correct_answer": 222, "events": [["submit", 476752]], "time_left_end": "155", "answered_time": 476752, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-7"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "155", "question_time_start": 476752, "question": "7+14+38", "correct_answer": 59, "events": [["submit", 476875]], "time_left_end": "155", "answered_time": 476875, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-8"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "155", "question_time_start": 476875, "question": "39+168", "correct_answer": 207, "events": [["submit", 477006]], "time_left_end": "155", "answered_time": 477006, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-9"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "155", "question_time_start": 477007, "question": "76+644", "correct_answer": 720, "events": [["submit", 477122]], "time_left_end": "155", "answered_time": 477122, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-10"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "155", "question_time_start": 477123, "question": "3+4+8+43", "correct_answer": 58, "events": [["submit", 477509]], "time_left_end": "155", "answered_time": 477509, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-11"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "155", "question_time_start": 477510, "question": "3+3+9+87", "correct_answer": 102, "events": [["submit", 478092]], "time_left_end": "154", "answered_time": 478092, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-12"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "154", "question_time_start": 478092, "question": "97+19", "correct_answer": 116, "events": [["submit", 478390]], "time_left_end": "154", "answered_time": 478390, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-13"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "154", "question_time_start": 478390, "question": "3+17+48", "correct_answer": 68, "events": [["submit", 478793]], "time_left_end": "153", "answered_time": 478793, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-14"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "153", "question_time_start": 478794, "question": "4+34+38", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 479939]], "time_left_end": "152", "answered_time": 479939, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-15"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "152", "question_time_start": 479939, "question": "19+67", "correct_answer": 86, "events": [["submit", 480191]], "time_left_end": "152", "answered_time": 480191, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-16"}}}, "block_4": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 480191, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "152", "question_time_start": 480191, "question": "3+56+59", "correct_answer": 118, "events": [["submit", 480460]], "time_left_end": "152", "answered_time": 480460, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-17"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "152", "question_time_start": 480460, "question": "53+463", "correct_answer": 516, "events": [["submit", 480708]], "time_left_end": "152", "answered_time": 480708, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-18"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "152", "question_time_start": 480708, "question": "7+16+39", "correct_answer": 62, "events": [["submit", 480921]], "time_left_end": "151", "answered_time": 480921, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-19"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "151", "question_time_start": 480922, "question": "38+56", "correct_answer": 94, "events": [["submit", 481123]], "time_left_end": "151", "answered_time": 481123, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-20"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "151", "question_time_start": 481123, "question": "58+836", "correct_answer": 894, "events": [["submit", 481324]], "time_left_end": "151", "answered_time": 481324, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-21"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "151", "question_time_start": 481324, "question": "6+3+7+17", "correct_answer": 33, "events": [["submit", 481524]], "time_left_end": "151", "answered_time": 481524, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-22"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "151", "question_time_start": 481524, "question": "9+29+73", "correct_answer": 111, "events": [["submit", 481741]], "time_left_end": "150", "answered_time": 481741, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-23"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "150", "question_time_start": 481741, "question": "37+74+96+83", "correct_answer": 290, "events": [["submit", 481974]], "time_left_end": "150", "answered_time": 481974, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-24"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "150", "question_time_start": 481974, "question": "7+3+4+34", "correct_answer": 48, "events": [["submit", 482223]], "time_left_end": "150", "answered_time": 482223, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-25"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "150", "question_time_start": 482224, "question": "54+83", "correct_answer": 137, "events": [["submit", 482446]], "time_left_end": "150", "answered_time": 482446, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-26"}}}, "block_5": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 482446, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "150", "question_time_start": 482446, "question": "9+78+86", "correct_answer": 173, "events": [["submit", 482659]], "time_left_end": "150", "answered_time": 482659, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-27"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "150", "question_time_start": 482659, "question": "77+49", "correct_answer": 126, "events": [["submit", 482905]], "time_left_end": "149", "answered_time": 482905, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-28"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "149", "question_time_start": 482906, "question": "3+3+9+68", "correct_answer": 83, "events": [["submit", 483143]], "time_left_end": "149", "answered_time": 483143, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-29"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "149", "question_time_start": 483143, "question": "14+758", "correct_answer": 772, "events": [["submit", 483378]], "time_left_end": "149", "answered_time": 483378, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-30"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "149", "question_time_start": 483378, "question": "48+777", "correct_answer": 825, "events": [["submit", 483592]], "time_left_end": "149", "answered_time": 483592, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-31"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "149", "question_time_start": 483593, "question": "7+26+43", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 483827]], "time_left_end": "148", "answered_time": 483827, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-32"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "148", "question_time_start": 483828, "question": "39+14+48+44", "correct_answer": 145, "events": [["submit", 484038]], "time_left_end": "148", "answered_time": 484038, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-33"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "148", "question_time_start": 484038, "question": "9+3+8+27", "correct_answer": 47, "events": [["submit", 484362]], "time_left_end": "148", "answered_time": 484362, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-34"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "148", "question_time_start": 484362, "question": "6+87+88", "correct_answer": 181, "events": [["submit", 484560]], "time_left_end": "148", "answered_time": 484560, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-35"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "148", "question_time_start": 484560, "question": "14+56", "correct_answer": 70, "events": [["submit", 484725]], "time_left_end": "147", "answered_time": 484725, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-36"}}}, "block_6": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 484726, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "147", "question_time_start": 484726, "question": "14+37+46+43", "correct_answer": 140, "events": [["submit", 484874]], "time_left_end": "147", "answered_time": 484874, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-37"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "147", "question_time_start": 484874, "question": "7+3+9+13", "correct_answer": 32, "events": [["submit", 484993]], "time_left_end": "147", "answered_time": 484993, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-38"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "147", "question_time_start": 484993, "question": "9+87+29", "correct_answer": 125, "events": [["submit", 485093]], "time_left_end": "147", "answered_time": 485093, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-39"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "147", "question_time_start": 485093, "question": "43+823", "correct_answer": 866, "events": [["submit", 485179]], "time_left_end": "147", "answered_time": 485179, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-40"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "147", "question_time_start": 485179, "question": "8+6+6+97", "correct_answer": 117, "events": [["submit", 485276]], "time_left_end": "147", "answered_time": 485276, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-41"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "147", "question_time_start": 485276, "question": "4+36+29", "correct_answer": 69, "events": [["submit", 485392]], "time_left_end": "147", "answered_time": 485392, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-42"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "147", "question_time_start": 485393, "question": "73+33", "correct_answer": 106, "events": [["submit", 485494]], "time_left_end": "147", "answered_time": 485494, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-43"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "147", "question_time_start": 485494, "question": "99+276", "correct_answer": 375, "events": [["submit", 485593]], "time_left_end": "147", "answered_time": 485593, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-44"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "147", "question_time_start": 485594, "question": "3+99+16", "correct_answer": 118, "events": [["submit", 485692]], "time_left_end": "147", "answered_time": 485692, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-45"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "147", "question_time_start": 485693, "question": "68+89", "correct_answer": 157, "events": [["submit", 485793]], "time_left_end": "146", "answered_time": 485793, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-46"}}}, "block_7": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 485793, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "146", "question_time_start": 485793, "question": "9+17+56", "correct_answer": 82, "events": [["submit", 485877]], "time_left_end": "146", "answered_time": 485877, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-47"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "146", "question_time_start": 485877, "question": "8+8+3+74", "correct_answer": 93, "events": [["submit", 485975]], "time_left_end": "146", "answered_time": 485975, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-48"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "146", "question_time_start": 485976, "question": "18+217", "correct_answer": 235, "events": [["submit", 486079]], "time_left_end": "146", "answered_time": 486079, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-49"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "146", "question_time_start": 486080, "question": "9+93+67", "correct_answer": 169, "events": [["submit", 486164]], "time_left_end": "146", "answered_time": 486164, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-50"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "146", "question_time_start": 486164, "question": "9+3+8+28", "correct_answer": 48, "events": [["submit", 486264]], "time_left_end": "146", "answered_time": 486264, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-51"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "146", "question_time_start": 486264, "question": "27+77+84+77", "correct_answer": 265, "events": [["submit", 486376]], "time_left_end": "146", "answered_time": 486376, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-52"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "146", "question_time_start": 486376, "question": "53+254", "correct_answer": 307, "events": [["submit", 486475]], "time_left_end": "146", "answered_time": 486475, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-53"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "146", "question_time_start": 486475, "question": "3+27+83", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["submit", 486593]], "time_left_end": "146", "answered_time": 486593, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-54"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "146", "question_time_start": 486594, "question": "44+77", "correct_answer": 121, "events": [["submit", 486776]], "time_left_end": "145", "answered_time": 486776, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-55"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "145", "question_time_start": 486777, "question": "64+58", "correct_answer": 122, "events": [["submit", 486923]], "time_left_end": "145", "answered_time": 486923, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-56"}}}, "block_8": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 486923, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "145", "question_time_start": 486923, "question": "6+29+69", "correct_answer": 104, "events": [["submit", 487295]], "time_left_end": "145", "answered_time": 487295, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-57"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "145", "question_time_start": 487295, "question": "9+6+7+43", "correct_answer": 65, "events": [["submit", 487446]], "time_left_end": "145", "answered_time": 487446, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-58"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "145", "question_time_start": 487446, "question": "7+7+4+23", "correct_answer": 41, "events": [["submit", 487595]], "time_left_end": "145", "answered_time": 487595, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-59"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "145", "question_time_start": 487595, "question": "7+39+59", "correct_answer": 105, "events": [["submit", 487779]], "time_left_end": "144", "answered_time": 487779, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-60"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "144", "question_time_start": 487779, "question": "58+27", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 488012]], "time_left_end": "144", "answered_time": 488012, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-61"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "144", "question_time_start": 488012, "question": "99+18+26+36", "correct_answer": 179, "events": [["submit", 488179]], "time_left_end": "144", "answered_time": 488179, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-62"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "144", "question_time_start": 488179, "question": "3+77+89", "correct_answer": 169, "events": [["submit", 488295]], "time_left_end": "144", "answered_time": 488295, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-63"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "144", "question_time_start": 488295, "question": "83+726", "correct_answer": 809, "events": [["submit", 488376]], "time_left_end": "144", "answered_time": 488376, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-64"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "144", "question_time_start": 488376, "question": "99+638", "correct_answer": 737, "events": [["submit", 488463]], "time_left_end": "144", "answered_time": 488463, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-65"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "144", "question_time_start": 488463, "question": "96+58", "correct_answer": 154, "events": [["submit", 488614]], "time_left_end": "144", "answered_time": 488614, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-66"}}}, "block_9": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 488614, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "144", "question_time_start": 488614, "question": "6+16+39", "correct_answer": 61, "events": [["submit", 489412]], "time_left_end": "143", "answered_time": 489412, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-67"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "143", "question_time_start": 489412, "question": "57+84", "correct_answer": 141, "events": [["submit", 489531]], "time_left_end": "143", "answered_time": 489531, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-68"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "143", "question_time_start": 489531, "question": "83+28+74+23", "correct_answer": 208, "events": [["submit", 489651]], "time_left_end": "143", "answered_time": 489651, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-69"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "143", "question_time_start": 489651, "question": "99+874", "correct_answer": 973, "events": [["submit", 489762]], "time_left_end": "142", "answered_time": 489762, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-70"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "142", "question_time_start": 489762, "question": "8+37+43", "correct_answer": 88, "events": [["submit", 489861]], "time_left_end": "142", "answered_time": 489861, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-71"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "142", "question_time_start": 489861, "question": "34+249", "correct_answer": 283, "events": [["submit", 489998]], "time_left_end": "142", "answered_time": 489998, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-72"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "142", "question_time_start": 489998, "question": "3+29+53", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 490146]], "time_left_end": "142", "answered_time": 490146, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-73"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "142", "question_time_start": 490146, "question": "3+7+8+69", "correct_answer": 87, "events": [["submit", 490246]], "time_left_end": "142", "answered_time": 490246, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-74"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "142", "question_time_start": 490246, "question": "7+9+4+24", "correct_answer": 44, "events": [["submit", 490364]], "time_left_end": "142", "answered_time": 490364, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-75"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "142", "question_time_start": 490364, "question": "84+96", "correct_answer": 180, "events": [["submit", 490478]], "time_left_end": "142", "answered_time": 490478, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-76"}}}, "block_10": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 490479, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "142", "question_time_start": 490479, "question": "93+949", "correct_answer": 1042, "events": [["submit", 490612]], "time_left_end": "142", "answered_time": 490612, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-77"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "142", "question_time_start": 490612, "question": "8+4+3+18", "correct_answer": 33, "events": [["submit", 490746]], "time_left_end": "141", "answered_time": 490746, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-78"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "141", "question_time_start": 490746, "question": "48+999", "correct_answer": 1047, "events": [["submit", 490883]], "time_left_end": "141", "answered_time": 490883, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-79"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "141", "question_time_start": 490883, "question": "3+36+36", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 491046]], "time_left_end": "141", "answered_time": 491046, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-80"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "141", "question_time_start": 491046, "question": "28+18+53+18", "correct_answer": 117, "events": [["submit", 491596]], "time_left_end": "141", "answered_time": 491596, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-81"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "141", "question_time_start": 491597, "question": "3+54+94", "correct_answer": 151, "events": [["submit", 491679]], "time_left_end": "141", "answered_time": 491679, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-82"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "141", "question_time_start": 491680, "question": "8+64+93", "correct_answer": 165, "events": [["submit", 491781]], "time_left_end": "140", "answered_time": 491781, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-83"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "140", "question_time_start": 491782, "question": "56+99", "correct_answer": 155, "events": [["submit", 491880]], "time_left_end": "140", "answered_time": 491880, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-84"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "140", "question_time_start": 491880, "question": "6+3+8+79", "correct_answer": 96, "events": [["submit", 492063]], "time_left_end": "140", "answered_time": 492063, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-85"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "140", "question_time_start": 492064, "question": "86+83", "correct_answer": 169, "events": [["submit", 492245]], "time_left_end": "140", "answered_time": 492245, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-86"}}}, "block_11": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 492245, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "140", "question_time_start": 492245, "question": "6+4+8+47", "correct_answer": 65, "events": [["submit", 492430]], "time_left_end": "140", "answered_time": 492430, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-87"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "140", "question_time_start": 492431, "question": "54+468", "correct_answer": 522, "events": [["submit", 492631]], "time_left_end": "140", "answered_time": 492631, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-88"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "140", "question_time_start": 492631, "question": "7+38+24", "correct_answer": 69, "events": [["submit", 492663]], "time_left_end": "140", "answered_time": 492663, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-89"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "140", "question_time_start": 492663, "question": "8+26+18", "correct_answer": 52, "events": [["submit", 492797]], "time_left_end": "139", "answered_time": 492797, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-90"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "139", "question_time_start": 492797, "question": "6+48+66", "correct_answer": 120, "events": [["submit", 492930]], "time_left_end": "139", "answered_time": 492930, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-91"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "139", "question_time_start": 492930, "question": "43+13", "correct_answer": 56, "events": [["submit", 493131]], "time_left_end": "139", "answered_time": 493131, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-92"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "139", "question_time_start": 493131, "question": "3+9+7+97", "correct_answer": 116, "events": [["submit", 493314]], "time_left_end": "139", "answered_time": 493314, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-93"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "139", "question_time_start": 493314, "question": "24+599", "correct_answer": 623, "events": [["submit", 493316]], "time_left_end": "139", "answered_time": 493316, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-94"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "139", "question_time_start": 493316, "question": "18+54+98+63", "correct_answer": 233, "events": [["submit", 493464]], "time_left_end": "139", "answered_time": 493464, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-95"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "139", "question_time_start": 493464, "question": "13+23", "correct_answer": 36, "events": [["submit", 493501]], "time_left_end": "139", "answered_time": 493501, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-96"}}}, "block_12": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 493501, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "139", "question_time_start": 493501, "question": "48+559", "correct_answer": 607, "events": [["submit", 493630]], "time_left_end": "139", "answered_time": 493630, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-97"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "139", "question_time_start": 493630, "question": "8+9+9+18", "correct_answer": 44, "events": [["submit", 493665]], "time_left_end": "139", "answered_time": 493665, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-98"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "139", "question_time_start": 493665, "question": "8+99+14", "correct_answer": 121, "events": [["submit", 493782]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 493782, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-99"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 493782, "question": "46+96+46+88", "correct_answer": 276, "events": [["submit", 493830]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 493830, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-100"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 493830, "question": "9+4+7+88", "correct_answer": 108, "events": [["submit", 493948]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 493948, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-101"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 493949, "question": "24+254", "correct_answer": 278, "events": [["submit", 493996]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 493996, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-102"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 493996, "question": "9+67+63", "correct_answer": 139, "events": [["submit", 494114]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 494114, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-103"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 494114, "question": "4+44+57", "correct_answer": 105, "events": [["submit", 494149]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 494149, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-104"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 494149, "question": "84+59", "correct_answer": 143, "events": [["submit", 494265]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 494265, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-105"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 494265, "question": "87+94", "correct_answer": 181, "events": [["submit", 494283]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 494283, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-106"}}}, "block_13": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 494283, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 494283, "question": "49+133", "correct_answer": 182, "events": [["submit", 494416]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 494416, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-107"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 494416, "question": "16+58+78+73", "correct_answer": 225, "events": [["submit", 494416]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 494416, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-108"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 494416, "question": "8+94+13", "correct_answer": 115, "events": [["submit", 494501]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 494501, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-109"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 494501, "question": "28+539", "correct_answer": 567, "events": [["submit", 494616]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 494616, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-110"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 494616, "question": "6+8+8+16", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 494698]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 494698, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-111"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 494699, "question": "7+4+7+96", "correct_answer": 114, "events": [["submit", 494816]], "time_left_end": "137", "answered_time": 494816, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-112"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "137", "question_time_start": 494816, "question": "9+58+79", "correct_answer": 146, "events": [["submit", 494935]], "time_left_end": "137", "answered_time": 494935, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-113"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "137", "question_time_start": 494936, "question": "8+23+24", "correct_answer": 55, "events": [["submit", 495020]], "time_left_end": "137", "answered_time": 495020, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-114"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "137", "question_time_start": 495020, "question": "77+24", "correct_answer": 101, "events": [["submit", 495030]], "time_left_end": "137", "answered_time": 495030, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-115"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "137", "question_time_start": 495030, "question": "83+94", "correct_answer": 177, "events": [["submit", 495117]], "time_left_end": "137", "answered_time": 495117, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-116"}}}, "block_14": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 495117, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "137", "question_time_start": 495117, "question": "9+6+8+54", "correct_answer": 77, "events": [["submit", 495180]], "time_left_end": "137", "answered_time": 495180, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-117"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "137", "question_time_start": 495181, "question": "7+9+4+28", "correct_answer": 48, "events": [["submit", 495394]], "time_left_end": "137", "answered_time": 495394, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-118"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "137", "question_time_start": 495394, "question": "28+86+87+29", "correct_answer": 230, "events": [["submit", 495531]], "time_left_end": "137", "answered_time": 495531, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-119"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "137", "question_time_start": 495531, "question": "76+738", "correct_answer": 814, "events": [["submit", 495631]], "time_left_end": "137", "answered_time": 495631, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-120"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "137", "question_time_start": 495632, "question": "3+49+33", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 495897]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 495897, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-121"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 495898, "question": "8+73+67", "correct_answer": 148, "events": [["submit", 495998]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 495998, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-122"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 495998, "question": "68+46", "correct_answer": 114, "events": [["submit", 496064]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 496064, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-123"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 496064, "question": "37+443", "correct_answer": 480, "events": [["submit", 496147]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 496147, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-124"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 496147, "question": "8+46+26", "correct_answer": 80, "events": [["submit", 496301]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 496301, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-125"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 496302, "question": "89+64", "correct_answer": 153, "events": [["submit", 496399]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 496399, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-126"}}}, "block_15": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 496399, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 496399, "question": "4+14+36", "correct_answer": 54, "events": [["submit", 496546]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 496546, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-127"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 496546, "question": "59+987", "correct_answer": 1046, "events": [["submit", 496634]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 496634, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-128"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 496634, "question": "3+33+78", "correct_answer": 114, "events": [["submit", 496715]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 496715, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-129"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 496715, "question": "93+757", "correct_answer": 850, "events": [["submit", 496814]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 496814, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-130"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 496814, "question": "6+6+4+59", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 496895]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 496895, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-131"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 496896, "question": "3+57+27", "correct_answer": 87, "events": [["submit", 496980]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 496980, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-132"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 496980, "question": "97+79", "correct_answer": 176, "events": [["submit", 497069]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 497069, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-133"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 497069, "question": "64+13+84+18", "correct_answer": 179, "events": [["submit", 497132]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 497132, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-134"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 497132, "question": "8+8+4+54", "correct_answer": 74, "events": [["submit", 497212]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 497212, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-135"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 497214, "question": "73+56", "correct_answer": 129, "events": [["submit", 497319]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 497319, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-136"}}}, "block_16": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 497319, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 497319, "question": "38+273", "correct_answer": 311, "events": [["submit", 497397]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 497397, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-137"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 497398, "question": "57+324", "correct_answer": 381, "events": [["submit", 497467]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 497467, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-138"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 497467, "question": "67+59", "correct_answer": 126, "events": [["submit", 497551]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 497551, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-139"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 497551, "question": "7+48+24", "correct_answer": 79, "events": [["submit", 497651]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 497651, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-140"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 497652, "question": "7+66+59", "correct_answer": 132, "events": [["submit", 497997]], "time_left_end": "134", "answered_time": 497997, "user_answer": "'", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-141"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "134", "question_time_start": 497998, "question": "9+4+7+36", "correct_answer": 56, "events": [["submit", 498649]], "time_left_end": "134", "answered_time": 498649, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-142"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "134", "question_time_start": 498649, "question": "4+6+3+38", "correct_answer": 51, "events": [["submit", 498816]], "time_left_end": "133", "answered_time": 498816, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-143"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "133", "question_time_start": 498817, "question": "6+18+66", "correct_answer": 90, "events": [["submit", 499050]], "time_left_end": "133", "answered_time": 499050, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-144"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "133", "question_time_start": 499050, "question": "97+94+54+38", "correct_answer": 283, "events": [["submit", 499182]], "time_left_end": "133", "answered_time": 499182, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-145"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "133", "question_time_start": 499183, "question": "63+67", "correct_answer": 130, "events": [["submit", 499266]], "time_left_end": "133", "answered_time": 499266, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-146"}}}, "block_17": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 499267, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "133", "question_time_start": 499267, "question": "7+13+24", "correct_answer": 44, "events": [["submit", 499447]], "time_left_end": "133", "answered_time": 499447, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-147"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "133", "question_time_start": 499448, "question": "99+979", "correct_answer": 1078, "events": [["submit", 499603]], "time_left_end": "133", "answered_time": 499603, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-148"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "133", "question_time_start": 499604, "question": "7+6+7+68", "correct_answer": 88, "events": [["submit", 499750]], "time_left_end": "132", "answered_time": 499750, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-149"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "132", "question_time_start": 499751, "question": "7+59+63", "correct_answer": 129, "events": [["submit", 499900]], "time_left_end": "132", "answered_time": 499900, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-150"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "132", "question_time_start": 499900, "question": "34+94", "correct_answer": 128, "events": [["submit", 500100]], "time_left_end": "132", "answered_time": 500100, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-151"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "132", "question_time_start": 500100, "question": "49+46+66+16", "correct_answer": 177, "events": [["submit", 500485]], "time_left_end": "132", "answered_time": 500485, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-152"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "132", "question_time_start": 500485, "question": "6+67+73", "correct_answer": 146, "events": [["submit", 500535]], "time_left_end": "132", "answered_time": 500535, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-153"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "132", "question_time_start": 500535, "question": "84+983", "correct_answer": 1067, "events": [["submit", 500654]], "time_left_end": "132", "answered_time": 500654, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-154"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "132", "question_time_start": 500654, "question": "3+4+9+24", "correct_answer": 40, "events": [["submit", 500717]], "time_left_end": "132", "answered_time": 500717, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-155"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "132", "question_time_start": 500718, "question": "99+97", "correct_answer": 196, "events": [["submit", 500831]], "time_left_end": "131", "answered_time": 500831, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-156"}}}, "block_18": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 500831, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "131", "question_time_start": 500831, "question": "84+27+43+97", "correct_answer": 251, "events": [["submit", 501004]], "time_left_end": "131", "answered_time": 501004, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-157"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "131", "question_time_start": 501004, "question": "47+773", "correct_answer": 820, "events": [["submit", 501067]], "time_left_end": "131", "answered_time": 501067, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-158"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "131", "question_time_start": 501068, "question": "79+29", "correct_answer": 108, "events": [["submit", 501184]], "time_left_end": "131", "answered_time": 501184, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-159"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "131", "question_time_start": 501185, "question": "8+3+8+18", "correct_answer": 37, "events": [["submit", 501237]], "time_left_end": "131", "answered_time": 501237, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-160"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "131", "question_time_start": 501237, "question": "6+59+79", "correct_answer": 144, "events": [["submit", 501402]], "time_left_end": "131", "answered_time": 501402, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-161"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "131", "question_time_start": 501402, "question": "79+127", "correct_answer": 206, "events": [["submit", 501417]], "time_left_end": "131", "answered_time": 501417, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-162"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "131", "question_time_start": 501417, "question": "9+43+14", "correct_answer": 66, "events": [["submit", 501601]], "time_left_end": "131", "answered_time": 501601, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-163"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "131", "question_time_start": 501601, "question": "9+93+78", "correct_answer": 180, "events": [["submit", 501602]], "time_left_end": "131", "answered_time": 501602, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-164"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "131", "question_time_start": 501602, "question": "4+3+4+83", "correct_answer": 94, "events": [["submit", 501756]], "time_left_end": "130", "answered_time": 501756, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-165"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "130", "question_time_start": 501756, "question": "33+93", "correct_answer": 126, "events": [["submit", 501767]], "time_left_end": "130", "answered_time": 501767, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-166"}}}, "block_19": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 501767, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "130", "question_time_start": 501767, "question": "99+29", "correct_answer": 128, "events": [["submit", 501882]], "time_left_end": "130", "answered_time": 501882, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-167"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "130", "question_time_start": 501882, "question": "6+4+3+83", "correct_answer": 96, "events": [["submit", 501998]], "time_left_end": "130", "answered_time": 501998, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-168"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "130", "question_time_start": 501999, "question": "9+36+78", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["submit", 502114]], "time_left_end": "130", "answered_time": 502114, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-169"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "130", "question_time_start": 502114, "question": "57+517", "correct_answer": 574, "events": [["submit", 502200]], "time_left_end": "130", "answered_time": 502200, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-170"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "130", "question_time_start": 502201, "question": "67+27+18+27", "correct_answer": 139, "events": [["submit", 502335]], "time_left_end": "130", "answered_time": 502335, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-171"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "130", "question_time_start": 502335, "question": "4+88+84", "correct_answer": 176, "events": [["submit", 503187]], "time_left_end": "129", "answered_time": 503187, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-172"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "129", "question_time_start": 503188, "question": "6+68+88", "correct_answer": 162, "events": [["submit", 503320]], "time_left_end": "129", "answered_time": 503320, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-173"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "129", "question_time_start": 503320, "question": "27+364", "correct_answer": 391, "events": [["submit", 503503]], "time_left_end": "129", "answered_time": 503503, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-174"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "129", "question_time_start": 503503, "question": "4+8+7+99", "correct_answer": 118, "events": [["submit", 503670]], "time_left_end": "129", "answered_time": 503670, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-175"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "129", "question_time_start": 503671, "question": "28+39", "correct_answer": 67, "events": [["submit", 503784]], "time_left_end": "128", "answered_time": 503784, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-176"}}}, "block_20": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 503784, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "128", "question_time_start": 503784, "question": "38+47", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 503902]], "time_left_end": "128", "answered_time": 503901, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-177"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "128", "question_time_start": 503902, "question": "9+36+24", "correct_answer": 69, "events": [["submit", 504018]], "time_left_end": "128", "answered_time": 504018, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-178"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "128", "question_time_start": 504019, "question": "7+4+3+93", "correct_answer": 107, "events": [["submit", 504118]], "time_left_end": "128", "answered_time": 504118, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-179"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "128", "question_time_start": 504118, "question": "9+58+23", "correct_answer": 90, "events": [["submit", 505318]], "time_left_end": "127", "answered_time": 505318, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-180"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "127", "question_time_start": 505319, "question": "63+259", "correct_answer": 322, "events": [["submit", 505586]], "time_left_end": "127", "answered_time": 505586, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-181"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "127", "question_time_start": 505586, "question": "7+6+7+28", "correct_answer": 48, "events": [["submit", 505718]], "time_left_end": "126", "answered_time": 505718, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-182"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "126", "question_time_start": 505718, "question": "34+336", "correct_answer": 370, "events": [["submit", 505852]], "time_left_end": "126", "answered_time": 505852, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-183"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "126", "question_time_start": 505852, "question": "4+56+29", "correct_answer": 89, "events": [["submit", 505970]], "time_left_end": "126", "answered_time": 505970, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-184"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "126", "question_time_start": 505970, "question": "18+67+44+49", "correct_answer": 178, "events": [["submit", 506336]], "time_left_end": "126", "answered_time": 506336, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-185"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "126", "question_time_start": 506336, "question": "69+24", "correct_answer": 93, "events": [["submit", 506487]], "time_left_end": "126", "answered_time": 506487, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-186"}}}, "block_21": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 506487, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "126", "question_time_start": 506487, "question": "36+636", "correct_answer": 672, "events": [["submit", 507084]], "time_left_end": "125", "answered_time": 507084, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-187"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "125", "question_time_start": 507085, "question": "89+429", "correct_answer": 518, "events": [["submit", 507168]], "time_left_end": "125", "answered_time": 507168, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-188"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "125", "question_time_start": 507168, "question": "4+83+17", "correct_answer": 104, "events": [["submit", 507238]], "time_left_end": "125", "answered_time": 507238, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-189"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "125", "question_time_start": 507238, "question": "9+73+53", "correct_answer": 135, "events": [["submit", 507354]], "time_left_end": "125", "answered_time": 507354, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-190"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "125", "question_time_start": 507354, "question": "6+6+9+84", "correct_answer": 105, "events": [["submit", 507421]], "time_left_end": "125", "answered_time": 507421, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-191"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "125", "question_time_start": 507421, "question": "24+78+88+77", "correct_answer": 267, "events": [["submit", 507520]], "time_left_end": "125", "answered_time": 507520, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-192"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "125", "question_time_start": 507520, "question": "9+64+34", "correct_answer": 107, "events": [["submit", 507587]], "time_left_end": "125", "answered_time": 507587, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-193"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "125", "question_time_start": 507587, "question": "64+34", "correct_answer": 98, "events": [["submit", 507689]], "time_left_end": "125", "answered_time": 507689, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-194"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "125", "question_time_start": 507689, "question": "8+8+8+76", "correct_answer": 100, "events": [["submit", 507750]], "time_left_end": "124", "answered_time": 507750, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-195"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "124", "question_time_start": 507750, "question": "59+93", "correct_answer": 152, "events": [["submit", 507857]], "time_left_end": "124", "answered_time": 507857, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-196"}}}, "block_22": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 507857, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "124", "question_time_start": 507857, "question": "14+163", "correct_answer": 177, "events": [["submit", 507923]], "time_left_end": "124", "answered_time": 507923, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-197"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "124", "question_time_start": 507923, "question": "6+94+69", "correct_answer": 169, "events": [["submit", 508087]], "time_left_end": "124", "answered_time": 508087, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-198"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "124", "question_time_start": 508087, "question": "8+3+4+53", "correct_answer": 68, "events": [["submit", 508256]], "time_left_end": "124", "answered_time": 508256, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-199"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "124", "question_time_start": 508256, "question": "66+93+86+88", "correct_answer": 333, "events": [["submit", 508420]], "time_left_end": "124", "answered_time": 508420, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-200"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "124", "question_time_start": 508421, "question": "7+19+26", "correct_answer": 52, "events": [["submit", 508571]], "time_left_end": "124", "answered_time": 508571, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-201"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "124", "question_time_start": 508572, "question": "36+296", "correct_answer": 332, "events": [["submit", 508723]], "time_left_end": "124", "answered_time": 508723, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-202"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "124", "question_time_start": 508723, "question": "6+6+9+47", "correct_answer": 68, "events": [["submit", 508874]], "time_left_end": "123", "answered_time": 508874, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-203"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "123", "question_time_start": 508875, "question": "16+87", "correct_answer": 103, "events": [["submit", 509037]], "time_left_end": "123", "answered_time": 509037, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-204"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "123", "question_time_start": 509037, "question": "7+79+84", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["submit", 509204]], "time_left_end": "123", "answered_time": 509204, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-205"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "123", "question_time_start": 509205, "question": "48+99", "correct_answer": 147, "events": [["submit", 509422]], "time_left_end": "123", "answered_time": 509422, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-206"}}}, "block_23": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 509422, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "123", "question_time_start": 509422, "question": "3+68+76", "correct_answer": 147, "events": [["submit", 509506]], "time_left_end": "123", "answered_time": 509506, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-207"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "123", "question_time_start": 509506, "question": "26+16", "correct_answer": 42, "events": [["submit", 509618]], "time_left_end": "123", "answered_time": 509618, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-208"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "123", "question_time_start": 509618, "question": "6+7+9+83", "correct_answer": 105, "events": [["submit", 509704]], "time_left_end": "123", "answered_time": 509704, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-209"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "123", "question_time_start": 509704, "question": "36+183", "correct_answer": 219, "events": [["submit", 509821]], "time_left_end": "122", "answered_time": 509821, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-210"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "122", "question_time_start": 509821, "question": "3+4+6+27", "correct_answer": 40, "events": [["submit", 509884]], "time_left_end": "122", "answered_time": 509884, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-211"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "122", "question_time_start": 509885, "question": "99+978", "correct_answer": 1077, "events": [["submit", 510075]], "time_left_end": "122", "answered_time": 510075, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-212"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "122", "question_time_start": 510075, "question": "79+94+89+74", "correct_answer": 336, "events": [["submit", 510185]], "time_left_end": "122", "answered_time": 510185, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-213"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "122", "question_time_start": 510185, "question": "7+78+84", "correct_answer": 169, "events": [["submit", 510269]], "time_left_end": "122", "answered_time": 510269, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-214"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "122", "question_time_start": 510269, "question": "6+59+87", "correct_answer": 152, "events": [["submit", 510374]], "time_left_end": "122", "answered_time": 510374, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-215"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "122", "question_time_start": 510375, "question": "74+89", "correct_answer": 163, "events": [["submit", 510455]], "time_left_end": "122", "answered_time": 510455, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-216"}}}, "block_24": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 510456, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "122", "question_time_start": 510456, "question": "14+186", "correct_answer": 200, "events": [["submit", 510569]], "time_left_end": "122", "answered_time": 510569, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-217"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "122", "question_time_start": 510569, "question": "7+9+7+97", "correct_answer": 120, "events": [["submit", 510637]], "time_left_end": "122", "answered_time": 510637, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-218"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "122", "question_time_start": 510637, "question": "74+83", "correct_answer": 157, "events": [["submit", 510756]], "time_left_end": "121", "answered_time": 510756, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-219"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "121", "question_time_start": 510756, "question": "3+8+7+27", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 510839]], "time_left_end": "121", "answered_time": 510839, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-220"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "121", "question_time_start": 510839, "question": "94+458", "correct_answer": 552, "events": [["submit", 510956]], "time_left_end": "121", "answered_time": 510956, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-221"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "121", "question_time_start": 510957, "question": "6+16+49", "correct_answer": 71, "events": [["submit", 511018]], "time_left_end": "121", "answered_time": 511018, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-222"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "121", "question_time_start": 511018, "question": "9+69+57", "correct_answer": 135, "events": [["submit", 511142]], "time_left_end": "121", "answered_time": 511142, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-223"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "121", "question_time_start": 511142, "question": "4+74+47", "correct_answer": 125, "events": [["submit", 511222]], "time_left_end": "121", "answered_time": 511222, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-224"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "121", "question_time_start": 511222, "question": "64+47+36+46", "correct_answer": 193, "events": [["submit", 511403]], "time_left_end": "121", "answered_time": 511403, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-225"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "121", "question_time_start": 511404, "question": "86+93", "correct_answer": 179, "events": [["submit", 511605]], "time_left_end": "121", "answered_time": 511605, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-226"}}}, "block_25": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 511605, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "121", "question_time_start": 511605, "question": "66+939", "correct_answer": 1005, "events": [["submit", 511723]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 511723, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-227"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 511724, "question": "56+67+34+16", "correct_answer": 173, "events": [["submit", 511790]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 511790, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-228"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 511790, "question": "4+23+18", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 512006]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 512006, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-229"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 512006, "question": "4+99+84", "correct_answer": 187, "events": [["submit", 512139]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 512139, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-230"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 512139, "question": "8+4+8+88", "correct_answer": 108, "events": [["submit", 512207]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 512207, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-231"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 512207, "question": "9+19+53", "correct_answer": 81, "events": [["submit", 512325]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 512325, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-232"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 512325, "question": "73+73", "correct_answer": 146, "events": [["submit", 512405]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 512405, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-233"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 512406, "question": "7+4+7+47", "correct_answer": 65, "events": [["submit", 512521]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 512521, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-234"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 512521, "question": "14+797", "correct_answer": 811, "events": [["submit", 512589]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 512589, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-235"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 512590, "question": "33+36", "correct_answer": 69, "events": [["submit", 512723]], "time_left_end": "119", "answered_time": 512723, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-236"}}}, "block_26": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 512723, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "119", "question_time_start": 512723, "question": "8+89+84", "correct_answer": 181, "events": [["submit", 512789]], "time_left_end": "119", "answered_time": 512789, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-237"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "119", "question_time_start": 512790, "question": "6+17+38", "correct_answer": 61, "events": [["submit", 512893]], "time_left_end": "119", "answered_time": 512893, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-238"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "119", "question_time_start": 512893, "question": "8+4+4+68", "correct_answer": 84, "events": [["submit", 512955]], "time_left_end": "119", "answered_time": 512955, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-239"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "119", "question_time_start": 512956, "question": "66+38+87+33", "correct_answer": 224, "events": [["submit", 513152]], "time_left_end": "119", "answered_time": 513152, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-240"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "119", "question_time_start": 513153, "question": "3+7+6+63", "correct_answer": 79, "events": [["submit", 513423]], "time_left_end": "119", "answered_time": 513423, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-241"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "119", "question_time_start": 513423, "question": "96+633", "correct_answer": 729, "events": [["submit", 531878]], "time_left_end": "115", "answered_time": 531878, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-242"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "115", "question_time_start": 531879, "question": "58+636", "correct_answer": 694, "events": [["submit", 532079]], "time_left_end": "115", "answered_time": 532079, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-243"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "115", "question_time_start": 532080, "question": "6+44+97", "correct_answer": 147, "events": [["submit", 532412]], "time_left_end": "115", "answered_time": 532412, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-244"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "115", "question_time_start": 532412, "question": "78+27", "correct_answer": 105, "events": [["submit", 593544]], "time_left_end": "107", "answered_time": 593544, "user_answer": "105", "user_correct": "True", "score": "-243"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "107", "question_time_start": 593545, "question": "37+28", "correct_answer": 65, "events": [["submit", 600323]], "time_left_end": "100", "answered_time": 600323, "user_answer": "65", "user_correct": "True", "score": "-242"}}}, "block_27": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 600323, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "100", "question_time_start": 600324, "question": "8+6+9+59", "correct_answer": 82, "events": [["submit", 612876]], "time_left_end": "87", "answered_time": 612876, "user_answer": "72", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-243"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "87", "question_time_start": 612877, "question": "6+29+68", "correct_answer": 103, "events": [["submit", 628603]], "time_left_end": "72", "answered_time": 628603, "user_answer": "103", "user_correct": "True", "score": "-242"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "72", "question_time_start": 628603, "question": "6+6+9+53", "correct_answer": 74, "events": [["submit", 643704]], "time_left_end": "57", "answered_time": 643704, "user_answer": "74", "user_correct": "True", "score": "-241"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "57", "question_time_start": 643705, "question": "8+13+84", "correct_answer": 105, "events": [["submit", 649712]], "time_left_end": "51", "answered_time": 649712, "user_answer": "105", "user_correct": "True", "score": "-240"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "51", "question_time_start": 649712, "question": "4+39+29", "correct_answer": 72, "events": [["submit", 654660]], "time_left_end": "46", "answered_time": 654660, "user_answer": "72", "user_correct": "True", "score": "-239"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "46", "question_time_start": 654660, "question": "84+38+59+93", "correct_answer": 274, "events": [["calc_8", 658932], ["calc_4", 659327], ["calc_+", 660182], ["calc_3", 660648], ["calc_8", 661250], ["calc_+", 661896], ["calc_5", 662400], ["calc_9", 662784], ["calc_+", 663300], ["calc_9", 664020], ["calc_3", 664584], ["calc_=", 665200], ["submit", 671870]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "28", "answered_time": 671870, "user_answer": "274", "user_correct": "True", "score": "-238"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "28", "question_time_start": 671871, "question": "23+773", "correct_answer": 796, "events": [["submit", 679417]], "time_left_end": "21", "answered_time": 679417, "user_answer": "796", "user_correct": "True", "score": "-237"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "21", "question_time_start": 679417, "question": "34+689", "correct_answer": 723, "events": [["submit", 692712]], "time_left_end": "8", "answered_time": 692712, "user_answer": "713", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-238"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "8", "question_time_start": 692713, "question": "79+96", "correct_answer": 175, "events": []}}}}}